Hi Jun.As you know,I've asked you here today to discuss the future of our Self-Access Centre.
你好，琼。我今天找你来是想讨论自习室的未来。
We have to decide what we want to do about this very important resource for our English language students.
我们得决定如何处理这个对我们英语学生非常重要的资源。
So,can you tell me that the students think about this?
所以，你能告诉我学生们都是怎么想的吗？
Well,from the students' point of view,we would like to keep it.
从学生的角度看，我们需要保留它。
The majority of students say that they enjoy using it
大多数学生称自己很喜欢它，
because it provides a variation on the classroom routine and they see it as a pretty major component of their course,
因为它为常规的课程带来了变化，他们认为这是课程的重要部分，
but we would like to see some improvements to the quipment,particularly the computers;
但是我们希望设备能有所改进，特别是电脑。
there aren't enough for one each at the moment and we always have to share.
有时不能达到每个人使用一台，我们总是要和别人一起用。
Well yes,the teachers agree that it is a very valuable resource
是的，老师们认为这是非常有价值的资源，
but one thing we have noticed is that a lot of the students are using it to check their personal emails.
但是我注意到一件事，许多学生用它查看个人邮件。
We don't want to stop you students using it, but we think the computers should be used as a learning resource,not for emails.
我们不想阻止学生使用它，但是我们认为电脑应该当作一种学习资源，而不是查看电邮。